<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.objectforge.mascot.ACPFormEditor"
      label="The Mascot 2015 ACP Editor"
      version="2.1.4"
      provider-name="Object Forge Ltd."
      plugin="com.objectforge.mascot.ACPFormEditor"
      os="linux,macosx,win32"
      nl="en_GB,en_US">

   <description url="http://www.object-forge.com/eclipse/">
      The ACP Editor Plugin is a stuctured editor for the creation
and mainteneance of MASCOT 2015 SETs documents (*.macp files).
SETs are XML documents that capture the structure of MASCOT 2015
systems as expressed in ACP diagrams; MASCOT Mahcines read them
as configuration files.  For more information regarding MASCOT
2010 and MOJO (a refernece implementaion of a MASCOT 2015 Machine
in Java) please refer to the URL below.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Object Forge Ltd., 2002 - 2015
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      MOJO: A Java implementation of the MASCOT Machine
  Copyright - The Object Forge, 2002,2003,2010,2015 (www.object-forge.com)

  MOJO is licensed material and is the property of the Object Forge, UK.
  It is not freeware or shareware and is not subject to any open source 
  licenses except where noted.  It is supplied for evaluation and 
  educational purposes only; production installations require a license
  from the Object Forge.

  MOJO comes with the usual health warnings and the Object Forge offers no 
  warrantee either expicit or implied.  Users run MOJO at thier own risk; 
  Object Forge accepts no responsibility for any damage, loss, or 
  inconvenience arising either directly or indirectly from the use of
  this software. Please contact Object Forge with comments and licensing 
  queries at aupport@object-forge.com or visit our site at 
  www.object-forge.com.
   </license>

   <url>
      <discovery label="Object Forge update site" url="http://www.object-forge.com/eclipse/update"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.forms"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.objectforge.mascot.ACPFormEditor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.4"/>

</feature>
